Don Walker Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
Guides to Special Collections in the Music Division of the Library of Congress
Don Walker Collection 1932-1984
ML31.W35
Walker, Don, 1907-1989
around 10,000 items 131 containers 52 linear feet
Music Division Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Don Walker was an arranger, orchestrator, composer, lyricist, and author, who was particularly known for his Broadway orchestrations. The collection, which relates primarily to his career, includes holograph music manuscripts and printed scores from musicals, radio and television shows, and films; scripts; personal and business papers that include correspondence, clippings, and financial documents; writings; and photographs.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically therein.
People
Walker, Don, 1907-1989. Works. Selections.; Walker, Don, 1907-1989--Archives.; Walker, Don, 1907-1989--Correspondence.; Walker, Don, 1907-1989--Manuscripts.; Walker, Don, 1907-1989--Photographs.; Walker, Don, 1907-1989.; Walker, Don, 1907-1989.
Subjects
Arrangers (Musicians)--United States.; Composers--United States.; Instrumentation and orchestration.; Motion picture music--Scores.; Music--Manuscripts--United States.; Musicals--Excerpts--Scores.; Musicals--United States.; Orchestrators--United States.; Popular music--United States.; Songs--Texts; Television music--Scores.
Form/Genre
Clippings (Information artifacts); Correspondence.; Photographic prints.; Programs (Documents); Scripts (Documents)
Administrative Information
Provenance
The Don Walker Collection was deposited at the Library of Congress by his widow, Audrey Walker, in October 2001. In December 2001, the portions of the deposit relating to the shows Courtin’ Time and The Girl in Pink Tights were converted to gift. In October 2002, the portions of the deposit relating to Hans Christian Andersen and Of Thee I Sing were converted to gift. Ms. Walker passed away in April 2003, and her will directed that the remainder of the collection be given to the Library.
Accruals
No further accruals are expected.
Transfers
Recordings have been transferred to the Library of Congress, Motion Picture, Broadcasting and Recorded Sound Division.
Related Material
The Don Walker Collection contains a small percentage of his output compared to the number of musicals he orchestrated. While many of the full scores appear to have been lost over the years, some have survived in various collections and his work has been preserved on many cast recordings. The Library of Congress Music Division holds the papers for many of the composers with whom Walker collaborated, some of which may contain Walker's full scores. These collections include: the Sigmund Romberg Collection,
Irving Berlin Collection
,
Richard Rodgers Collection
,
Cole Porter Collection
,
Vernon Duke Collection
,
Arthur Schwartz Papers
, Burton Lane Collection, Richard Adler Collection, and the
Leonard Bernstein Collection
.
Access and Restrictions
The Don Walker Collection is open to research. Researchers are advised to contact the Music Division prior to visiting in order to determine whether the desired materials will be available at that time.
Access to the collection is not restricted, and researchers may obtain single-copy reproductions of the unpublished and published materials contained therein, for research purposes. Obtaining additional copies of published material may be subject to provisions of the copyright law. Other uses of the collection, including performing, recording, or publishing of music materials or writings, may require the permission of the author(s) and their estates. Consult reference staff in the Performing Arts Reading Room for assistance in contacting the Walker estate.
Biographical Note
Date Event
1907, Oct. 28 Born Donald John Walker in Lambertville, New Jersey, only child of Thomas J. Walker and Blanche S. Walker (nee Basford)
circa 1920-circa 1929 Studied piano and pipe organ Organist, St. Andrews Episcopal Church Studied flute, clarinet, and tenor saxophone Started local dance band
1922, June 7 Graduated, Lambertville High School Salutarian of class
circa 1922-circa 1928 Played tenor sax in Don Walker’s Interfraternity Five Played solo clarinet in University of Pennsylvania marching band
1926 B.C.S. and B.S., Accountancy, Rider College of Business, Trenton, N.J.
1928 Member, honorary scholastic fraternity, Beta Gamma Sigma
1929 B.S., Economics, Wharton School, University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, Pa.
1929-1932 Arranger and assistant conductor of recordings (Victor), Fred Waring’s Pennsylvanians
1931, Mar. 14 Married Audrey Langrill Simpson of Moore Park, Toronto, Canada (died 2003)
1932, Mar. 8 Daughter Ann Audrey Walker born
1932-1933 Composer, arranger and conductor, Mask and Wig Productions, University of Pennsylvania Productions included Ruffneck and Out of the Blues
1933, Sept. 3 Son David Ellsworth Walker born
1933-1935 Head arranger, Al Goodman Orchestra (for radio shows Lucky Strike Program, Good Gulf Program and others)
1934 Co-orchestrator, Life Begins at 8:40 Co-orchestrated and composed two numbers, Caviar
1935 Co-orchestrator, At Home Abroad Co-orchestrator, May Wine
1935-1942 Head arranger for Frank Black at NBC
1935-1952 Staff arranger, Harms (sold to Chappell and Co.) Worked with Robert Russell Bennett, Hans Spialek, Conrad Salinger, Ted Royal
1936 Co-orchestrator, Ziegfeld Follies of 1936 Orchestrator, Forbidden Melody
1936-1951 Head arranger for Sigmund Romberg (for radio programs, operettas, concert tours, albums)
1937 Orchestrator, Hooray for What! Co-orchestrator, Three Waltzes
1938 Additional orchestrations, You Never Know Orchestrator, Leave it to Me!
1939 Musical director, conductor, arranger, Nice Goin’ Orchestrator, Stars in Your Eyes Co-orchestrator, George White’s Scandals
1940 Orchestrator, Two for the Show Co-orchestrator, Keep Off the Grass Co-orchestrator, Boys and Girls Together Orchestrator, Panama Hattie Orchestrator, Hold on to Your Hats Co-orchestrator, Hi Ya, Gentlemen Co-orchestrator, Walk with Music
1941 Orchestrator, Let’s Face It! Orchestrator, Best Foot Forward
1942 Co-orchestrator, Count Me In Orchestrator, By Jupiter
1943 Conductor and arranger, CBS radio program Only Yesterday Orchestrator, Something for the Boys
1944 Joined ASCAP Co-composer and orchestrator, Allah Be Praised! Co-orchestrator, On the Town
1945 Co-orchestrator, Carousel Composer, adaptor, co-orchestrator, Memphis Bound!
1946 Composer, Fabulous Doll
1947 Co-orchestrator, Finian’s Rainbow
1948 Co-orchestrator, Kiss Me Kate Co-orchestrator, Heaven on Earth Co-orchestrator, That’s the Ticket Some orchestrations, Inside U.S.A.
1948-1973 Founder, vice-president, president, Bucks County Playhouse, New Hope, Pennsylvania Composer and arranger, various productions of The Bucks County Revue Vice-president and director, Playhouse Inn
1949 Some orchestrations for, Miss Liberty; Touch and Go; Gentlemen Prefer Blondes; South Pacific Orchestrator, NBC television series The Admiral Broadway Revue
1950 Co-orchestrator, Great to Be Alive! Orchestrator, Call Me Madam Orchestrator, Bless You All
1951 Composed and orchestrated, Courtin’ Time Some orchestrations, The King and I
1952 Special orchestrations, Pal Joey (revival) Co-orchestrator, Of Thee I Sing (revival)
1953 Arranger and orchestrator, Wonderful Town Arranger and orchestrator, Me and Juliet Arranger and orchestrator, Agnes de Mille Dance Theatre
1954 Orchestrator, The Girl in Pink Tights Orchestrator, The Pajama Game Orchestrator, On Your Toes (revival)
1955 Orchestrator, Silk Stockings Orchestrator, Damn Yankees Co-orchestrator, Finian’s Rainbow (revival) Additional orchestrations, Catch a Star!
1956 Orchestrator, The Most Happy Fella Additional orchestrations, Happy Hunting
1957 Musical director and arranger, Your Hit Parade, NBC television show Orchestrator, The Music Man Composed and scored, Mistress of the Inn, Bucks County Playhouse (continued to work on the show through revised version, The Inn People (1972))
1957-1959 Lecturer, “Music Heard-Music Written,” Hunter College School of Adult Education
1958 Composed and orchestrated incidental music, Comic Strip Orchestrated, The Gift of the Magi (television musical) Musical supervisor and orchestrator, The Red Mill (television musical) Worked on novel The Bucket of Blood
1959 Orchestrator, First Impressions
1960 Orchestrator, Greenwillow Co-orchestrator, Finian’s Rainbow (revival) Orchestrator, The Unsinkable Molly Brown
1961 Orchestrator, The Gay Life
1962 Composed and orchestrated incidental music, The Beauty Part
1963 Orchestrator, She Loves Me Orchestrator, Here’s Love
1964 Orchestrator, What Makes Sammy Run Orchestrator, Anyone Can Whistle Orchestrator, Fiddler on the Roof
1965 Orchestrator, Baker Street Orchestrator, Flora, the Red Menace Orchestrator, Anya Scored A Thousand Clowns (film) Academy Award nominee for Scoring of Music–Adaption or Treatment, A Thousand Clowns
1966 Orchestrator, Cabaret
1967 Orchestrator, Hellzapoppin ‘67
1968 Orchestrator, The Happy Time Orchestrator, Zorba
1969 Co-composer and orchestrator, The Appointment (film) Co-composed incidental music, Angela
1970 Orchestrator, The Rothschilds
1971 Orchestrator, 70, girls, 70
1973 Orchestrator, Pajama Game (revival) Began project for Music Theatre International to adapt Italian and French operas for performance by American high schools and colleges
1974 Co-orchestrator, Lorelei Orchestrator, Shenandoah, at Goodspeed Opera House
1975 Orchestrator, Shenandoah Co-orchestrator, Jeeves Orchestrator, Hans Christian Andersen
1976 Orchestrator, The Baker’s Wife Orchestrator, Fiddler on the Roof (revival)
1978 Orchestrator, Angel
1978-1980 Adapted score, Ragtime Blues
1979 Orchestrator, The Most Happy Fella (revival)
1980 Orchestrator, The Music Man (revival) Orchestrator, The Barber of Guadalajara, adaption of Rossini’s The Barber of Seville in mariachi style
1981 Orchestrator, Fiddler on the Roof (revival)
1982 Orchestrator, The Little Prince and the Aviator Composed film score for Freedom
1982-1983 Worked on novel 6-Piece Quintet
1983 Orchestrator, Zorba (revival)
1984 Worked on memoir Men of Notes
1987 Orchestrator, Cabaret (revival)
1989, Sept. 13 Died, Mercer Medical Center, Trenton, New Jersey
Scope and Content Note
The Don Walker Collection spans the years 1932-1984 and primarily relates to Walker's professional career. It is organized into the following series: Personal and Business Papers, Writings, Photographs, and Music. The Personal and Business Papers series contains Walker’s files along with other items that were in miscellaneous folders and envelopes, or loose inside the boxes in which the collection had been shipped. Loose items relating to a particular topic or show were placed in the relevant folders in Walker's files. In addition, programs were placed in folders for their respective shows. The clippings file within this series consists of photocopies of all the loose newspaper clippings. In a few instances, items from one folder were removed and placed in either a pre-existing folder or a newly created one. In most cases, this was done so that correspondence for a significant figure could be clearly identified and placed together in one folder making it easier to find. For example, correspondence from Jerry Bock had been in the “Miscellaneous correspondence” and “Theatre people (corres.)” files, and correspondence from John Kander had been in “Correspondence from the 1960s,” “Correspondence from the 1980s,” and “Miscellaneous correspondence” files. Numbers in parentheses after a folder title indicates the number of folders with that title.
The Music series is divided into two subseries: Show Music and Non-Show Music. The former includes scores and scripts for musicals, radio and television shows, and films; and incidental music for straight plays. The show music is organized alphabetically by show title. Within a show, where all formats exist in quantity, items are first broken down by format, such as full score, piano-vocal score, part, script, and then alphabetically by song title (where appropriate) therein. In cases where there are various items in various formats, the entirety is organized by song title. Many scores were either combinations of, or could arguably be designated, one or more of the following: short score, piano-conductor score, piano-vocal score, vocal arrangement, reduced score, or lead sheet. Many folders contain multiple copies and various versions of the same piece, but there is no way to determine this through the finding aid.
Much of the Non-Show Music includes songs that were written for shows but, by all appearances, were arranged or used by Walker for recordings, concerts, or other events. This material is organized by the title of an individual work or, in a few cases, first by a particular project and then alphabetically by the works therein. In most cases, the project title was directly taken off Walker's folder or portfolio which contained the scores. Primary examples are: College Songs; deMille, Agnes (Dance Theatre); Glad Singers; Hartley Ray; Lindencroft Music; Oriental Suite; Rittman Study Material; Romberg, Sigmund; Songs (with Matt Dubinsky). Even though most of the music in this subseries is either composed or arranged by Walker, there is a significant portion which lacks a clear connection to Walker. Many of the published piano-vocal scores in this subseries include annotations by Walker reflecting his notes on how the song might be arranged. Most of the published piano-vocal scores that lacked annotations were not kept in the collection as they seemed to reveal nothing beyond the fact that Walker owned them.
The Writings series includes materials relating to two of his novels, portions from his incomplete memoir, course materials, and miscellaneous lyric sheets. The Photographs series includes portraits of Walker and photographs of his family.
Organization of the Don Walker Collection
The Don Walker Collection is organized in four series:
Personal and Business Papers
Writings
Photographs
Music
http://lccn.loc.gov/2013568037
Container List
- Personal and Business Papers (Box 1-20)
  - 70 girls 70 (Box 1)
  - 888 lease (Box 1)
  - 1970 New York material (Box 1)
  - Abbott, George (Box 1)
  - Active correspondence (Box 1)
  - Adams, Bret (Box 1)
  - Adams, Roger (Box 1)
  - Adler, Richard (Box 1)
  - Adler and Ross (Box 1)
  - Address and appointment books (Box 1)
  - The admiral Broadway revue (Box 1)
  - Agnes de Mille concert (2) (Box 1)
  - Allah be praised! (Box 1)
  - American federation of musicians (Box 1)
  - Angela (Box 1)
  - Ankles aweigh (Box 1)
  - Anya (Box 1)
  - Anyone can whistle (Box 1)
  - The appointment (Box 1)
  - Armed forces classification (Box 1)
  - Arnold Goland lyrics (Box 1)
  - ASCAP (Box 2)
  - Author's league copyrights (Box 2)
  - Babes in arms (Box 2)
  - Backlash (Box 2)
  - Baker Street (Box 2)
  - The baker's wife (Box 2)
  - The band wagon (Box 2)
  - Bank statements-chemical (Box 2)
  - The barber of Seville (Box 2)
  - Beat the band (Box 2)
  - The beauty part, Includes other minor work (Box 2)
  - Robert Russell Bennett inventory (Box 2)
  - Berlin, Irving (Box 2)
  - Best foot forward (Box 2)
  - Bio inquiries (Box 2)
  - Biography and work list (Box 2)
  - Bless you all (Box 2)
  - Bloomgarden, Kermit (Box 2)
  - Bock, Jerry (Box 2)
  - Bock and Harnick (Box 2)
  - Brisson, Freddie (Box 2)
  - Brisson, Griffith and Prince (Box 2)
  - British Copyright Museum (Box 3)
  - Bucks County community chest (Box 3)
  - Buck's County Playhouse (3) (Box 3)
  - Buck's County Playhouse articles (Box 3)
  - Buck's County Playhouse programs (Box 3)
  - Burning leaves-contract papers (Box 3)
  - A burst of summer (Box 3)
  - Business (Box 3)
  - Business correspondence (Box 3)
  - Business financial statements (Box 3)
  - Buttrio Square (Box 3)
  - By Jupiter (Box 3)
  - Cabaret (Box 3)
  - Call me madam (Box 3)
  - Can-can (Box 3)
  - Carnival in Flanders (Box 4)
  - Carousel (Box 4)
  - Cassidy, Jack (Box 4)
  - Catalogs, publications, lists (Box 4)
  - Chappell proposition (Box 4)
  - Check stubs (Box 4)
  - Clippings
    - Allah be praised (Box 4)
    - All's fair (Box 4)
    - Ankles aweigh (Box 4)
    - Anyone can whistle (Box 4)
    - Baker Street (Box 4)
    - The baker's wife (Box 4)
    - The barber of Guadalajara (Box 4)
    - Beat the band (Box 4)
    - The beauty part (Box 4)
    - Bless you all (Box 4)
    - A burst of summer (Box 4)
    - Cabaret (Box 4)
    - Can-can (Box 4)
    - Carousel (Box 4)
    - Courtin' time (Box 4)
    - Damn Yankees (Box 4)
    - The duchess misbehaves (Box 4)
    - Early to bed (Box 4)
    - Fiddler on the roof (Box 4)
    - Finian's rainbow (Box 4)
    - The gay life (Box 4)
    - Gentlemen prefer blondes (Box 4)
    - The girl in pink tights (Box 4)
    - Great to be alive (Box 4)
    - Greenwillow (Box 4)
    - Happy hunting (Box 4)
    - The happy time (Box 4)
    - Hello yourself (Box 4)
    - Her first Roman (Box 4)
    - Here's love (Box 4)
    - Hollywood pinafore; Memphis bound (Box 4)
    - Look, Ma, I'm dancin'! (Box 4)
    - Magazines (Box 5)
    - Maggie (Box 5)
    - Me and Juliet (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous (2) (Box 5)
    - Miss Liberty (Box 5)
    - The mistress of the inn (Box 5)
    - The most happy fella (Box 5)
    - The music man (Box 5)
    - Of thee I sing (Box 5)
    - The pajama game (Box 5)
    - Pal Joey (Box 5)
    - Park Avenue (Box 5)
    - Romberg, Sigmund (Box 5)
    - She loves me (Box 5)
    - Shenandoah (Box 5)
    - Silk stockings (Box 5)
    - Sunny river (Box 5)
    - A thousand clowns (Box 5)
    - Top banana (Box 5)
    - Touch and go (Box 5)
    - The unsinkable Molly Brown (Box 5)
    - Up in Central Park (Box 5)
    - What a day! (Box 5)
    - What makes Sammy run? (Box 5)
    - Windy city (Box 5)
    - Wish you were here (Box 5)
    - Zorba (Box 5)
  - Cohan, George M. (Box 5)
  - Comic strip (Box 5)
  - Concerts (Box 5)
  - Contracts, etc. (Box 5)
  - The cool mikado see also The mikado (Box 6)
  - Coots, J. Fred (Box 6)
  - Copyrights-general info (foley) (Box 6)
  - The countess of boot (Box 6)
  - Courtin' time (2) (Box 6)
  - Courtin' time-box office statements (Box 6)
  - Coward, Noel (Box 6)
  - Curtain going up (Box 6)
  - DaCapo (Box 6)
  - Damn Yankees (Box 6)
  - Dance me a song (Box 6)
  - Decca Records (Box 6)
  - Delilah see also The vamp (Box 6)
  - DeMille, Agnes (Box 6)
  - Don Camillo (Box 6)
  - Donald music inc.
    - 1973 (Box 7)
    - To December 1975 (2) (Box 7)
    - 1975-1977 (Box 7)
    - 1978, 1981, 1982 (Box 7)
    - 1979-1981 (2) (Box 7)
    - Bank statements (2) (Box 8)
  - Dreyfuss, Max see also Men of notes: Research (Box 8)
  - Dunham, Katherine (Box 8)
  - Early to bed (Box 8)
  - Ebb, Fred (Box 8)
  - Engel, Lehman (Box 8)
  - Extra pension (Box 8)
  - The fabulous doll (Box 8)
  - Farm bureau (co-op) (Box 8)
  - The farmer's wife (Box 8)
  - Fiddler on the roof (Box 8)
  - Fiddler on the roof-case (Box 8)
  - Fiddler on the roof-correspondence, etc. (Box 8)
  - Fiddler on the roof-royalties, release (Box 8)
  - Field, Ronald (Box 8)
  - Fields, Joseph (Box 8)
  - Financial reports, investments, and royalty statements (Box 8)
  - Financial statements (Box 9)
  - Finian's rainbow (Box 9)
  - First impressions (Box 9)
  - Flora the red menace-company (bills) (Box 9)
  - Forbidden melody (Box 9)
  - Ford dealer's show (Box 9)
  - Foreign royalties (Box 9)
  - Freedly, Vinton (Box 9)
  - The gay life (Box 9)
  - Gentlemen prefer blondes (Box 9)
  - The girl in pink tights (Box 9)
  - The glad singers (Box 9)
  - Gladiolus correspondence (Box 9)
  - Gladiolus-file for tax purposes (Box 9)
  - Glover, Joe (Box 9)
  - Go fight city hall (Box 9)
  - Go fight city hall-basic material (Box 9)
  - Songs with Arnold Goland see also Arnold Goland lyrics (Box 9)
  - Goodman, Bob (Box 10)
  - Gorney, Jay (Box 10)
  - Great to be alive! (Box 10)
  - Green, Johnny (Box 10)
  - Greene, Lawrence (Box 10)
  - Greenwillow (Box 10)
  - Grey, Joel (Box 10)
  - Griffith, Robert (Box 10)
  - Hammerstein II, Oscar (Box 10)
  - Hans Christian Andersen-contracts, bills, etc. see also HCA correspondence (Box 10)
  - The happiest days (Box 10)
  - The happy time (2) (Box 10)
  - Happy jazz band (Box 10)
  - Harburg, EY (Box 10)
  - Harnick, Sheldon (Box 10)
  - Hart, Lorenz (Box 10)
  - Hart, Moss (Box 10)
  - Hartley, Ray (Box 10)
  - Hastings, Hal (Box 10)
  - Hazel Flagg (Box 10)
  - HCA correspondence see also Hans Christian Andersen-contracts, bills, etc. (Box 10)
  - Hellzapoppin' (Box 10)
  - Henderson, Skitch (Box 10)
  - Her first Roman (Box 10)
  - Here's love (Box 10)
  - Hi ya, gentlemen (Box 11)
  - Historical material (Box 11)
  - Hoffman, Richard (Box 11)
  - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc. (Box 11)
  - Hoyt, Howard (Box 11)
  - Hyman, Joe (Box 11)
  - Illya darling (Box 11)
  - The inn people (Box 11)
  - The inn people-corresondence, script suggestions, etc. (Box 11)
  - The inn people-scripts (Box 11)
  - Insurance (other) (Box 11)
  - Jack lyrics (Box 11)
  - Jeffries, Anne (Box 11)
  - Jeeves (Box 11)
  - Kander, John (Box 11)
  - Kander and Ebb (Box 11)
  - Kiss me, Kate (Box 11)
  - "Lament for an innocent abroad" lyric (Box 11)
  - Laurents, Arthur (Box 11)
  - Leases (Box 11)
  - Lindsay, Howard and Russell Crouse (Box 11)
  - Little Jesse James (Box 11)
  - The little prince (Box 11)
  - Live correspondence (Box 11)
  - Loesser, Frank (Box 11)
  - The loft (Box 11)
  - Logan, Josh (Box 11)
  - Look homeward, angel (Box 11)
  - Look homeward, angel-contracts and bills (Box 11)
  - Look Ma, I'm dancin' (Box 11)
  - Loos, Anita (Box 11)
  - Lucky strike formula (Box 11)
  - MacDonald, Jeanette (Box 12)
  - Maggie (Box 12)
  - Manhattan merry-go-round (Box 12)
  - Martin, Hugh (Box 12)
  - Masteroff, Joe (Box 12)
  - May wine (Box 12)
  - Me and Juliet (Box 12)
  - Memorabilia (Box 12)
  - Memphis bound/pinafore (Box 12)
  - "Men behind the music" article (Box 12)
  - Mielziner, Jo (Box 12)
  - The mikado see also The cool mikado (Box 12)
  - Mills contracts/reports (Box 12)
  - Mills memos (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous arranging (bills) (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous Walker play notes and reviews (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous billings (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 12)
    - 1920 s
    - 1930 s
    - 1940 s
    - 1950 s
    - 1960 s
    - 1970 s
    - 1980 s
  - Miscellaneous papers (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous programs and publications (Box 13)
  - Miss Liberty (Box 13)
  - The mistress of the inn (2) (Box 13)
  - Moffett, Nick (Box 13)
  - Morrow, Doretta (Box 13)
  - The most happy fella (3) (Box 13)
  - The most happy fella-royalties (Box 13)
  - Mr. and Mrs. America (Box 13)
  - The music man (Box 13)
  - The music man-royalties, contracts, etc. (Box 13)
  - Music Publishers' Association (Box 13)
  - Music Theatre Inc. (Box 13)
  - My romance (Box 13)
  - New York personal (Box 13)
  - Newley, Anthony (Box 13)
  - Nicoll, Oliver research (Box 13)
  - No room at the inn (Box 14)
  - Nothing but the best (Box 14)
  - Of thee I sing (Box 14)
  - On the town (Box 14)
  - On with the show (Box 14)
  - On your toes (Box 14)
  - Only yesterday-programs ( 1944 ) (Box 14)
  - Opening billboard (Box 14)
  - Opening night notes (Box 14)
  - Opera project (Box 14)
  - Other contracts (Box 14)
  - Pajama game (Box 14)
  - Pal Joey (Box 14)
  - Park avenue (Box 14)
  - Personal correspondence (2) (Box 14)
  - Personal correspondence 1957-1959 (2) (Box 14)
  - Personal expenses (Box 14)
  - Personal notes and correspondence (Box 14)
  - The Philadelphia Inquirer Magazine (article) (Box 14)
  - Pincus, Mathilde (Box 14)
  - Playhouse Inn (2) (Box 15)